(ominous music)
(clock ticking)
(curtain flapping)
- Once there was
a boy named James,
my grandson,
a child who learned the weight
of goodbye far too young.
After his parents died,
he came to live with me
in a house of old wood
and ticking clocks.
(thunder rumbling)
A house full of memory.
(clock ticking)
Then death is a greedy visitor.
It never comes just once.
It returned
and it took his
very best friend.
I watched the boy's heart break.
So then I made a vow.
You will never
lose anyone again.
I worked.
I spent more and more
time in the basement,
a place forbidden to James.
Days turned to weeks
creating something,
something just for him.
Something which will
never say goodbye.
never belong to death.
Pinocchio.
(letters rattling)
(mysterious music)
(James knocking on door)
Not today. Thanks.
- Oh gosh, no, not again.
No. Come on.
This joke is so old it
should be in a nursing home.
(Mia laughs)
- [Mia] Um, Bye James.
- How's he holding up?
- [Mia] Oh, he had
a moment earlier,
but I think he'll be okay.
- And you?
- I'm good as can be.
Yeah, thanks.
Bye.
- Thanks for keeping
an eye on him lately.
(light solemn music)
(birds chirping)
- Zach, wait up.
(dramatic music)
(door creaks)
- Grab your coat, kiddo.
Bit of fresh air
will do us good.
Now come on.
It's always hard losing
someone you love.
Your mother, now
your best friend.
- Do you ever worry, Granddad,
about what happens after?
Like, when we die.
- All I worry about is you.
- I just, I wish
Zach was still here.
It doesn't feel
the same anymore.
- Well, maybe he is.
(gentle piano music)
I believe what makes you, you,
sticks around after and
moves into what surrounds us.
- Yeah, Dudley told me
that stuff's rubbish.
- I've seen Dudley pick
his nose and eat it too.
(both laughing)
Look up.
What do you see?
- Um, loads of stars.
- "There are more things in
heaven and earth, Horatio,
"than are dreamt of
in your philosophy."
It means life is full of
endless possibilities.
(light music)
(Geppetto coughing)
- Granddad, are you okay?
Are you okay? Do you want me to-
- I'm fine. Don't worry.
- You sure?
- Mm.
Fine.
We should get home soon.
I have something very
exciting to show you tomorrow.
(mysterious music)
(floor creaks)
(suspenseful music)
(footsteps pattering)
(door creaks)
(ominous music)
(light switch clicking)
(suspenseful music)
(dramatic music)
(ominous music)
(footsteps thudding)
(door creaking)
(door clicks shut)
(suspenseful music)
You sure there's nothing
else you remember?
(stairs creak)
James?
- Who are you talking to?
- Come down.
There's someone here
I want you to meet.
- Someone?
- Come, come.
(mysterious music)
- Is that what I saw upstairs?
- That'll be him.
- Where is he?
(ominous music)
- In there.
He's shy, I think.
(ominous music)
Come on out.
I want you to meet someone.
He's the boy I've been
telling you about.
(ominous music)
(Pinocchio's hand creaking)
Yes, him.
(ominous music)
(water splashes)
(mysterious music)
(dramatic music)
You're the first
person he's seen
other than me.
I think he wants
to be your friend.
(dramatic music)
- Stop! Go away!
Please stop!
- James, stop!
(James panting)
Listen to me, James.
- What the fuck was that?
- Calm down and
watch your language-
- No, no, no, no!
What was that? That
thing down there?
What? What is it?
- It's not a thing.
It's a who, James.
It's alive.
Things aren't always
what they seem,
life is not-
- What were you talking about?
- I know it's hard to believe,
but trust me in time, this
is all gonna make sense.
I didn't mean to scare you.
I just thought you
could use a friend.
I know he could.
- A friend?
With, with that thing?
- [Geppetto] This could be
good for the both of you.
(dramatic music)
- How long has he
been down there?
- [Geppetto] That's all
he's ever really known.
(door creaks)
Why don't you say hello?
(mysterious music)
- James.
- I'm Pinocchio.
Are we friends?
- Maybe. We'll see.
- James,
you can tell nobody about this.
Understood?
Good boy.
(mysterious music)
(playful music)
- You're not gonna get
my ship, Captain James.
- Oh, I'm gonna make
you walk the plank.
Okay. You got it?
- [Pinocchio] Mm-hmm.
- Your move.
(chess pieces clatter)
(bright music)
- Is that me?
- Yeah.
(cellphone buzzing)
Now.
- Dude.
What the fuck is that?
- [James] Nothing. Nothing.
It's just a doll Granddad made.
This one's biology.
- [Pinocchio] What is bilology?
- It's like why boys are
made different from you.
Organs and stuff.
- (gasps) Wow.
What else makes us different?
- Teeth, eyes, hair, skin.
I mean, there's lots of things.
- I wanna be just like you.
- (laughs) No, trust me.
You don't.
You're way cooler than me.
- What's this?
- Oh.
Uh...
- [TV Narrator] As the herd
follows the sea's plains,
danger lies in wait.
But in the presence
of a predator,
the herd will
protect one another.
- The herd will protect.
(buffalo grunting onscreen)
You are my herd.
(mysterious music)
- [TV Narrator] However,
sometimes the greatest danger
comes from within the group.
(door creaks)
(lion growls onscreen)
(mysterious music)
- [Pinocchio] James.
Why?
- You can't.
- I want to be with James.
- He's going to school tomorrow.
People won't react well.
- Because I don't have a penis?
- No, I don't know
what to say to that.
The world isn't ready for you.
Not yet.
(ominous music)
- Like 100 kg.
- Rubbish, mate.
- Pure muscle, it's just hidden.
Just need to do, like, a diet.
- Need some help with that?
- You can do that?
- [James] I could help you
lose five pounds, easy.
- How?
- I just cut off a right arm.
- Ah!
(James laughing)
(inhaler whooshes)
(insect buzzing)
- Ah! Fuck!
(groans) Ouch, my head.
(suspenseful music)
(Pinocchio exhales)
(mysterious music)
(Pinocchio gasps)
(mysterious music continues)
(electricity crackles)
(dramatic music)
(Pinocchio gasps)
- Child, come closer.
My splinters hurt.
- You talk?
- Who else would tell
the truth he hides?
- What are you?
- I am your Wood Mother.
Geppetto may have
carved our bodies,
but I will shape your mind.
- Are you stuck there?
- As are you.
- I'm not stuck.
- The strings may be invisible,
but you are still his puppet.
- I'm no puppet.
I'm just like James.
I'm a real boy.
- (laughs) Your
nose betrays you.
The creator says you are real.
He doesn't look
at you like James.
You want his arms to
hold you, not hide you,
then come closer
and I'll whisper how to be real.
You need skin,
blood, teeth, hair.
Take them, wear them.
- Ew, that's disgusting.
I'm not doing that.
(Wood Mother laughing)
- Then stay caged,
little puppet,
whilst James walks in sunlight.
Unless I'm wrong.
Prove it.
(dramatic music)
(glass shatters)
(bright music)
- Wow.
(birds chirping)
(school bell rings)
(children chattering)
(door creaks)
- Pinocchio?
Oh, there you are.
(solemn music)
- [Pinocchio] Who are these?
- Oh, they're my best mates.
- [Pinocchio] Best mates?
- Yeah.
It's like a friend forever.
Someone you protect
and you never break a
promise to and stuff.
- Are we best mates?
- Put out your hand.
We've got to do this to
make it official first.
A super secret handshake.
Now first we slap our
fist both sides, like,
and then...
That's, that's right.
Good guess.
(pen scratching)
(light piano music)
- Are you going again tomorrow?
- Yeah.
And you're coming with me.
But you've gotta make one
of those promises first.
No matter what, no
one can see you move.
Just be like a doll, yeah?
- Easy.
(bright music)
- [James] Why are
you all tied up?
- [Pinocchio] Father
says it's to protect me.
- Oh, I've gotta meet Dudley.
Oh, here you go.
- [Pinocchio] Ouch.
- Oh, you're heavy.
- No, I'm not.
(mysterious music)
- [Geppetto] Dentist
after school, James.
- See you later, Granddad!
- See you, kiddo.
(suspenseful music)
(insect buzzing)
- Whoa, this is amazing.
Wow.
- [James] That's Trey and
that's where he lives.
He's a proper asshole.
- Asshole.
Hey James.
What's an asshole?
- Uh, I'll explain another time.
- Ah.
Oh.
So,
is he an ass or
the hole of an ass?
(light music)
(children chattering)
- Hey!
(ominous music)
- So everyone,
how do we determine
what makes someone bad?
- Bad?
- [Teacher] Each of you
have an internal conscience,
like a compass
guiding you towards what
you believe is right.
(school bell rings)
(students chattering)
- Just trying to make sure
fucking obliterated to bits.
Hey, let's go, dick weed.
- One second.
I can't take you in there.
Just stay here and
don't mess anything up.
- James, are you
talking to your bag?
- Coming.
Yeah, it's gonna be out.
- Strange.
- Have his arm ripped off.
(students chattering)
(mysterious music)
- Up, down.
Up, down.
Don't worry, James.
I won't let anyone see me.
Best friend handshake, yeah.
(energetic music)
(footsteps thumping)
(woman screams)
(Pinocchio gasps)
(metal clangs)
Oh no.
Are you okay?
(ominous music)
Oh my God. Watch out.
(metal clangs)
(woman screams)
(Pinocchio gasps)
Jesus. I've gotta go.
Promise you won't
tell anyone about me.
(playful music)
What are they for?
- Ages ago we used to
play pretend superheroes.
Dudley wanted to be that guy.
This one, ugly one is Dudley.
- Wow, that looks just like him.
- Yeah, I know.
It means I could just
stop him and he's-
(door rumbling)
Shit.
Don't move.
- Okay.
- Yo, bro, you've been
very hard to find today.
Playing with your
little dolls again?
- They aren't dolls.
- He's gotten himself a
bigger one, hasn't he?
(laughs) Yeah.
Hey, hey.
- No, no, no.
(both laughing)
- Get off me!
- Your granddad's
rich as fuck anyway,
with all that old money.
Think of this as tax.
- No wonder Mia dumped you.
- Oh. (laughs)
- Listen, the only
reason why she likes you,
because you are an
even bigger loser
than your dead ass friend.
- Oh!
(spit splatters)
(James grunting)
- Hold him while I fuck
this whole shit up.
- What the fuck are you doing?
No!
God, I fucking hate you!
I fucking hate you!
Don't touch him! Get off me!
(suspenseful music)
- You tell anyone
about this, dickhead,
I'll kill you.
- What the fuck, Trey?
- The kid started it.
- Hey, you need
to fucking leave.
All of you!
James.
They're pretty bad guys, right?
- The worst.
I wish they were all dead.
Thanks Mia.
- Come here.
(solemn piano music)
Hey, who's this little fella?
- Oh, that's Pinocchio.
He's special.
- Well, how about I go find
Dudley and you can show us?
- [James] What do you
mean you went to the gym?
- Apparently it has to
be in this secret area.
- James, what? Whoa!
What is that?
Oh, your granddad's made a
proper freaky one this time.
Oh, look at that nose.
- Okay guys, there is
something wanted to show you.
Promise it stays between us.
- Yeah, sure. Promise.
- [Mia] Yeah, sure.
- Pinocchio, it's
okay. They can see.
Pinocchio.
- No fucking way!
Okay, this is
officially the coolest
and creepiest thing
I've ever seen.
How's he doing that?
- Uh...
- Come on, man. What is it?
- Is this some like,
AI thing, James?
- Yeah, exactly.
Uh, the wires are hidden in
the brain chip in his head.
- Brain chip?
- The CPU or whatever.
No matter what,
my granddad can never
ever find out I have him.
It cost like, one
million pounds.
(timer beeping)
Crap. Sorry guys, gotta go.
I'm late for my dentist.
- Mate, mate.
Mate, this ain't over!
I'm coming straight
'round after!
- It's really gonna
hurt, isn't it?
Can we use some of that, um?
Can we use some of that
stuff to put me to sleep?
- We can't.
Just be brave, alright?
- Are you sure?
- It'll be over
before you know it
and you'll have perfect
teeth just like mine.
Come on. Open wide.
All done.
- Ah.
- That will really help.
Shouldn't feel anything now.
(light squeaking)
(James groaning)
(tools buzzing)
(tooth rattles)
- [Driver] So, how
are you feeling James?
- Ah, it hurts like hell.
- [Driver] Ah, you'll
be fine by tomorrow.
- Are you okay?
(ominous music)
(glass shatters)
(metal clanging)
Help me! Ah!
(car alarm beeping)
Oh no.
James?
(telephone ringing)
- Hello, hello?
- [Caller] Is this the
Geppetto residence?
- Who's this?
- [Caller] I'm calling
from St. Mary's Hospital.
Your grandchild's
been in an accident.
(distant siren wailing)
- You've got a visitor.
How's he getting on?
- Yeah, no, he's fine.
Just superficial wounds.
But he does have signs
of mild concussion.
But I think with a little
bit of sleep he'll be okay.
- [Nurse] What happened?
- Drunk driver.
And the same one as last year.
That reminds me, I need
to go and check on him
'cause he's in pretty bad shape.
Wish me luck.
- Good luck.
(solemn piano music)
Oh James, please don't die.
You're my best friend.
And best friends,
best friends,
best friends protect each other.
Yeah.
- You're just seeing
things, Larry.
It's all in your head.
(playful music)
- [Pinocchio] Dr.
Robin, there you are.
(doors bang)
(Pinocchio gasps)
Whoo!
(mysterious music)
(gurney clanging)
(suspenseful music)
Oh no.
(metal clanging)
Fuckity fuck.
(suspenseful music)
(bucket clatters)
Ew.
(Pinocchio breathing heavily)
Where have you gone?
- [Doctor] The paralysis is
temporary, so try not to worry.
I'm gonna get
something for the pain.
(suspenseful music)
Found you.
There you are.
(monitor beeping)
(suspenseful music)
(Pinocchio humming)
(ominous music)
(mysterious music)
(monitor beeping quickly)
(dramatic music)
- Hello.
You're the bad man.
You're pure evil.
It's all your fault.
James is my friend.
He's my best friend.
I'm going to take care of him.
So I need to make to you dead.
- No, no.
- Silence will get you nowhere.
The herd will protect
one another, bad man.
- Oh!
- And your reign
of terror is over.
- Oh, ah!
- You deserve to be made dead.
- Ah!
(ominous music)
- So Mr. Drunk,
off to hell you go!
(grunts) Take this!
This is what happens
to bad people!
This is for James!
(patient screaming)
(Pinocchio laughing)
This is for James!
(blood squelching)
(Pinocchio laughing)
Like it's raining.
♪ Rain, rain, go away ♪
♪ Come again another day ♪
The world won't miss
someone like you.
(dramatic music)
(patient screaming)
Stop complaining.
Why won't you just die?
(suspenseful music)
(patient shouting)
(Pinocchio gasps)
Organs and stuff.
(haunting music)
Bilology.
I can use this.
I'm going to be a real boy.
I'm going to be just like James.
It's cool.
You have so much of this stuff.
Yes, yes! This so fun! (laughs)
So much of this stuff.
(laughs) Wow.
(ominous music)
(Pinocchio laughing)
James is safe.
Your reign of terror is over.
For James!
(Pinocchio laughs)
(mysterious music)
(water splashing)
(playful music)
(Pinocchio whistling)
(Pinocchio gasps)
(clipboard clatters)
Uh-oh.
(mysterious music)
- It was right
after the dentist.
- He just came out of nowhere?
- [James] Yeah.
(mysterious music)
(door creaking)
(James coughing)
(dramatic music)
Oh!
- I'll call the nurse.
- No, no, no. (clears throat)
It seems to have
calmed down now.
- [Geppetto] Are you sure?
- (coughs) Yeah,
I should be fine.
- You alright, James?
We got your scans back
and you are good to go.
- Already?
- Yeah.
No, he's absolutely fine.
Just lots of rest. Okay?
- Thanks.
- Let's get you home, kiddo.
I'll grab your bag.
- Wait, wait, I'll grab my bag.
- Okay.
You're being very strange.
(mysterious music)
(woman sobbing)
- Oh, did you see him?
- But he was bad.
- Look who's come to see you.
- James, your granddad told us.
- James!
- All right, kiddos.
I'm heading out to
get pizzas in a bit.
So no filling up on crap.
- Thanks Granddad.
- Yeah, your AI thing.
- Oh shit!
Let's go start that thing!
- Reckon you could be
a bit louder, Dudley?
Remember, secret.
- Ugh! What kind of
AI doll leaks shit?
- I'm always on.
- Are you leaking?
- They're my organs.
They're making me real.
- Ugh! What the hell?
James, mate, why is it leaking?
Ugh.
- I'll explain later, just,
just get it back before
Granddad returns.
- James.
- Come on, Dudley.
Come on.
Dudley, quick.
Bring him over.
(suspenseful music)
Come on, man.
- I need to stay
and protect you.
- You can't.
Granddad can't know.
This is our secret, remember?
- But you're in danger.
(ominous music)
- James, what's all this?
(James speaks faintly)
- Yes, Lord James.
- Let go of me!
Filthy boy! Don't you dare!
(both shouting)
I wanna go home! Ah!
- No, Pinocchio, stop!
(Pinocchio shouting)
- Dudley one, Pinocchio nil.
- James, please.
- I'm sorry.
When Granddad's
gone, I'll come back.
Promise.
(inhaler whooshes)
(suspenseful music)
- Hurry up, come on.
- Coming.
- Oh, we can play the
synchronized protector.
- Everything all right?
- I'll find you in a minute.
Uh, sick.
- You feel sick?
- No, like a good sick.
Like I feel good. Yeah.
- Right.
You remember what we
spoke about, right?
- Yeah.
I know, Granddad.
- Alright, kiddo.
Take it easy on yourself.
- Yeah.
(ominous music)
- [Pinocchio] Stupid
bloody rope! Ah!
(Pinocchio's body thuds)
- Oh, there you are,
little splinter.
Come closer.
Tell your old Wood
Mother what rots you.
- They're hiding me
because I'm different, but,
but James is in danger.
- Danger? That child?
From who?
- Lots of bad people.
One almost killed him.
So, so I had to make him dead.
- My clever, clever boy.
Protecting your brother.
That is real love.
- Was that bad?
- Bad? Killing him?
Of course not.
You were just protecting him.
And that was only the beginning.
You know what to do with
the other bad people now.
Yes?
- Get rid of them too?
- Precisely!
One by one
until they're all gone.
Then James will be safe.
And remember,
if you want to be truly real,
take what they have.
Piece by piece
(cellphone ringing)
to make yourself whole.
(dramatic music)
- [Pinocchio] Woo-hoo!
Whoa!
(Pinocchio groans)
- Yes, in here.
This will work.
- And why are we in
this dusty old place?
- Because I think Geppetto
is hiding something
and I want to know
what's on these tapes.
(film projector whirring)
- I was right.
My belief that the
soul, life, energy,
whatever you want to call it,
does indeed remain after
death and can be harnessed.
This could lead to a kind of
rebirth that allows us to,
to cheat death.
I heard this strange wailing,
but just come, watch.
(dramatic music)
- What is that?
- After shaping it
into moving forward,
it's progressing faster
and with help will
gain motor function.
It's learning incredibly fast.
(ominous music)
My work has taken a turn.
The subject is dangerous.
Born evil.
It's developed an
obsession to be human
and escape these walls.
I need to reset.
(puppet muffled screaming)
(gunshot blasts)
- James, did you know
about any of this?
- Why can't it just make noise?
Why does it gotta make you shit?
Look at that.
- Yeah, play this one.
It was two days ago.
(inhaler whooshes)
(suspenseful music)
- So far no experiment
has recalled
one memory from its prior life,
till then I can't be confident
it is indeed a form of rebirth.
My next experiment, Pinocchio,
will be exposed to
external stimuli
to help evoke those memories.
Tonight he meets my grandson.
(suspenseful music)
(door creaking)
- Now where are you?
(ominous music)
Oh, get off! What the hell?
(Pinocchio groans)
Who are you?
- Name's Cricket.
Your Wood Mother sent me
to keep you on the right
path and obey the grownups.
- [Pinocchio] To help James?
- That's right.
The world's full of
rot you need to stop,
like whoever is in that room.
- [Pinocchio] Oh my God.
- And remember, piece by piece,
we'll take what's left.
Everything you need to be real.
- [Pinocchio] Thanks Cricket.
Let's do this
for James.
- Let's make that bitch choke.
(dramatic music)
(suspenseful music)
Look.
She's collecting them.
(Pinocchio gasps)
- That horrible woman.
(footsteps pattering)
(ominous music)
(chair creaking)
(dramatic music)
(Pinocchio shouting)
(dentist muffled screaming)
Open wide.
(dramatic music)
(both grunting)
- [Cricket] Take this! (grunts)
- Nasty tooth pulling bitch!
(Pinocchio shouts)
(ominous music)
You won't hurt James again.
For James.
(dramatic music)
(dentist whimpering)
I saw what you did to James.
You can't hide behind
those masks any longer.
(dentist whimpering)
(mysterious music)
This will help.
You shouldn't feel a thing.
(Pinocchio shouts)
(dramatic music)
(dentist whimpering)
- Yeah, smash that grin
off her shitty face.
Make sure she says cheese.
- Thanks Cricket.
Just be brave.
It'll be over
before you know it.
Never hurt James again,
you horrible lady!
(Pinocchio shouts)
(dentist screaming)
(Pinocchio shouting)
(dentist whimpering)
- Good lad.
Now let's give you a smile.
(dentist shouting)
- Shh, these are mine now.
(ominous music)
(Pinocchio laughing)
Hey, now I have
the perfect smile,
just like you.
(ominous music)
(Pinocchio laughing)
James.
I can't wait to
show James. (laughs)
- [James] Pinocchio?
- Oh my God.
I bet that creepy ass thing's
in this room somewhere.
- Why didn't you tell us, James?
- [Dudley] You said
it was a robot.
(Dudley wheezing)
(inhaler whooshes)
- Oh no, he's missing.
Call, call my phone.
- What? Why?
- Quick, just do it.
(cellphone ringing)
Pinocchio?
- James!
- Does he have teeth?
- [James] What are you doing?
- I'm stopping all
the bad people!
- You're stopping them how?
- Everyone keeps hurting you,
so I have to protect you.
Look.
- Holy fuck!
- No, no, no, Pinocchio.
That's not what I meant.
- Oh.
- What?
- Oh, he's muted now.
No more. No more.
- More?
Oh, kill more!
- Oh fuck.
- Oh my God.
- [Mia] Good job, Dudley.
- Wait, come back!
I need to kill you!
- No, Pinocchio, stop.
- Come back!
Come back here with that lady!
- Pinocchio, that's not-
- Come on, guys.
We've gotta go stop him.
That's the church
behind my dentist.
- James? Mia?
(mysterious music)
(door creaking)
Shit!
Pinocchio!
(dramatic music)
- Found you, asshole.
- James, answer your phone now!
Where have you taken him?
(water splashes)
- One day you're gonna
have to come around,
you know what I'm saying?
- No, stop it.
- Stop being so lame, come on.
- (scoffs) Annoying.
- Yo.
- Asshole.
- Wait, wait!
- [Pinocchio] Nasty boy.
(ominous music)
(muffled techno music)
- Logan!
It's too cold.
Logan!
(Logan humming)
(mysterious music)
(air whooshing)
(Georgia screaming)
(Pinocchio shouting)
(Georgia gasping)
(dramatic music)
- [Pinocchio] Oh no, you don't!
(ominous music)
(bones crack)
(heart beating)
(Georgia screaming)
(ominous music)
- Swim, swim, swim,
little guppy. (laughs)
(dramatic music)
- I didn't know they
keep whales in here.
Here I come, naughty girl!
Swim, swim, stupid lady.
(Pinocchio laughing)
(ominous music)
I'll fucking kill you, bitch!
(Georgia muffled screaming)
This nasty bully.
Cricket! Cricket, where are you?
Ah!
- [Cricket] I'm
coming. I'm coming.
I'm three inches tall.
Cut me some slack.
- Stop squiggling!
I need to send you to hell!
- Pay attention, Pinocch.
Time for a science lesson.
(haunting music)
Zap, zap, motherfucker! (laughs)
(electricity zapping)
(Pinocchio and Cricket laughing)
(suspenseful music)
(muffled techno music)
(Pinocchio coughing)
- Hi Logan.
(Logan screaming)
(dramatic music)
Come on, you know it's me.
(Logan screaming)
- The eyes. The eyes.
Not the tongue.
The eyes are what you need.
- Give me that!
(eyeball squelches)
Yeah!
- Pop 'em in, kid.
One more step to
being just like James.
- Teeth.
Eyes.
Lots of things.
(suspenseful music)
- Pinocchio?
Where the hell is he?
Oh fuck!
(Dudley retches)
Oh, fucking hell.
- Mia, call the police.
- And tell them what, Dudley?
That a homicidal
doll is on the loose?
- He's not a
homicidal doll, okay?
He's just, he's
trying to protect me.
- Sure, James.
- He, he's a killer.
I mean, look, he's
literally killing.
He's literally killing.
(Dudley retches)
- James.
- It's all my,
it's all my fault!
- James, is there anyone
that you can think of
that he might target next?
- Oh fuck! Oh shit!
Trey!
- Trey? Dudley!
(mysterious music)
(window squeaking)
(ominous music)
(water splashing)
(door creaking)
- [Pinocchio] Ooh la la.
(mysterious music)
(gasps) She cut her penis off.
What the hell?
(ominous music)
- Wait, what?
She's getting dressed already?
Let me show you how
it's done, Pinocch.
Let's go, you dirty bitch.
(ominous music)
You stupid skank.
Give me that!
(ominous music)
(Amanda screaming)
- [Pinocchio] What
are you doing?
- [Cricket] This hair,
it's gonna make you real!
(blood squelches)
(ominous music)
That hair isn't yours to keep.
(Amanda screaming)
- [Pinocchio] Oh, oh! My nose!
Get off it! Please
get off my nose!
Get off it now! Get off it!
Ow! Ow!
(Pinocchio's body thuds)
(ominous music)
Come back!
- Come on, kid.
Real boys don't quit.
- [Pinocchio] Come back!
(Amanda screaming)
- Amanda?
(dramatic music)
(Amanda screaming)
(Pinocchio grunting)
(dramatic music)
(Amanda screaming)
- [Pinocchio] This is my hair!
Stop screaming!
It's mine!
- What the fuck?
(Amanda screaming)
- It's mine!
(dramatic music)
(Pinocchio's body thuds)
(ominous music)
(scalp squelches)
- Oh.
No, you? You're
James' fucking doll.
- Yeah, 'tis me.
- No! Fuck this!
(Pinocchio grunts)
(Trey shouting)
(Pinocchio laughing)
- Look at me. It's real.
- No, get the fuck away from me.
- I'm not a doll, Trey.
(Pinocchio shouts)
And I'm not a puppet.
- Oh fuck!
- You won't take
dreams away from me.
- Help!
(Trey muttering)
- You can't hurt James anymore.
It's too late to lie now.
(ominous music)
You're my best friend.
You're such a nice guy.
I don't want to kill you.
(blood squelching)
- Cricket, one.
Bald skank, zero.
(playful music)
(car rumbling)
- We're at least
10 minutes away.
What if he?
- Oh shit!
Oh, shit, shit, shit.
Your crazy granddad's
calling, James.
- Dudley, what the hell?
Why'd you answer?
- [Geppetto] Hey.
- Hey, hey Granddad.
- Where are you?
- Yeah, we just,
we just had to stop off
at Mia's really quick.
Oh, we just had to-
- Mia! Mia!
Left! Left!
Trey's is that way.
- [Mia] I know where
my ex-boyfriend lives.
- Dudley!
- Gimme the phone. Go.
I know what to do.
Yeah, so.
- You hung up?
- Yeah, now he's definitely
not gonna suspect anything.
Is he?
(suspenseful music)
(cellphone thuds)
- [Geppetto] Little shit.
(mysterious music)
(door creaks)
(footsteps thudding)
(Pinocchio breathing)
- I remember when you were
just a little splinter.
Now, beautiful.
Complete.
Finally
a real boy.
(ominous music)
One hell of a glow up, kid.
- I'm gorgeous.
(jaunty big band music)
♪ Oh, you beautiful doll ♪
♪ You great big beautiful doll ♪
♪ Let me put my
arms around you ♪
♪ I could never
live without you ♪
♪ Oh, you beautiful doll ♪
♪ You great big beautiful doll ♪
♪ If you ever leave me
how my heart will ache ♪
♪ I wanna hug you,
but I need a break ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
- Hmm, what do you think?
This hat suit me, Pinocch?
(jaunty big band music)
(suspenseful music)
(door creaks)
(insects buzzing)
(suspenseful music)
(ominous music)
(blood squelching)
- [Pinocchio] Look, Father,
I made a puppet too.
(ominous music)
- Is that your granddad's car?
- [Dudley] Oh yeah.
There he goes.
- James.
- Off to wreck more lives.
- Pinocchio.
Quick, Mia. Go after him.
- [Dudley] They're both killers.
(tires screeching)
Oh!
(suspenseful music)
(Pinocchio's body thudding)
(Pinocchio shouting)
- They were going to hurt James.
(footsteps thudding)
But why?
(door slams shut)
(Wood Mother laughing)
Why, that nasty, lying bitch.
You lied to me.
Why did you lie to me?
- Messed up, haven't
you, little splinter?
- This is all your fault.
- You carved this path yourself.
- You got me to do
those bad things.
I'm not gonna let
you trick me anymore.
- Greedy.
Dissatisfied with what you are.
I should be where you are!
Look at me when I'm speaking!
- You've made everyone hate me.
- Because you're bad, Pinocchio.
Bad as the ones you butchered.
- We raised you to be
a good boy, Pinocch.
- Oh, get off me,
Cricket! (groans)
There you are!
(Pinocchio shouting)
- Don't you dare!
(mallet thuds)
- Leave him alone!
- No! You dumb bitch!
(dramatic music)
Nasty Wood Mother!
I'll teach you,
you stupid asshole!
Wrinkly shit!
(Wood Mother shouting)
(mallet thudding)
(Pinocchio yelling)
(Wood Mother gasping)
(Pinocchio breathing heavily)
(water dripping)
- There's something
I need to show you.
You want to be real
because of your past.
Come with me.
(door creaks)
- [Pinocchio] What
is this place?
- [Geppetto] It's
where you were created.
(switch clangs)
(electricity zaps)
- [Pinocchio] Oh my God.
(mysterious music)
(ominous music)
- It feeds through the roots,
growing as it siphons
their life force
infusing itself into the wood.
The same wood I then harvest.
That's right.
(dramatic music)
(mallet thudding)
(wood splintering)
You are the mere existence.
When their life
ended, yours began.
(ominous music)
- Where did they come from?
(crow cawing)
(footsteps thudding)
(ominous music)
- Once I realized I
could harvest it, I
began to study them.
Trying to understand
how they worked,
trying to perfect the process.
There were many failures.
- [Pinocchio] It's moving.
- One of which was
particularly dangerous.
(puppet growling)
So I had to keep it locked away.
(ominous music)
But then you came along,
my perfect creation.
You had so much potential.
- Potential?
For what?
- To prove that I was right.
That we could be reborn.
That we can master death.
But ultimately you're as much
a failure as the rest of them.
- Oh.
- [Dudley] Your granddad
is a killer, James.
What could we do
against a killer?
- You're absolutely sure?
- Yes.
You saw what he did
to that other doll.
He doesn't deserve to die, okay?
- James, like, maybe
it's better if he does.
- I agree. Dudley's right.
- He was doing it to protect me!
- [Dudley] But your granddad
is a murderer, James.
- Whatever, stay here then.
- Stop.
Not listening at all, are you?
(mysterious music)
- It's strange.
Both of us wanting to
be like each other.
- Who did I come from?
- A young boy.
A dear friend of James'.
- (gasps) Zach?
- Pinocchio came from
Zach?
- What the hell?
- I'd hoped Zach and
James' friendship
would show that
death isn't the end.
- That's it.
This is just getting
worse and worse.
I'm getting out of this place.
Your granddad is
an absolute freak.
- But I don't want to die.
- Your death is
what's best for James.
- No.
(dramatic music)
- [Dudley] He's gone
mental and he has to die.
- [Geppetto] Fucking kid.
- I, I can't listen to him.
We need to save him.
(suspenseful music)
- James, help me please!
- Pinocchio?
- James, Mia,
Father's gone crazy.
- I know. I don't
want you to die.
Okay? You're in danger.
(suspenseful music)
- James! Mia!
Help me!
(gunshot blasts)
(Mia screams)
- Oh!
- Oh fuck!
(both gasping)
(ominous music)
- You bitch.
(vomit bubbles)
(gunshot blasts)
- Dudley, no!
(dramatic music)
- [Mia] He locked the door.
- Untie me quick.
- Now!
- I know somewhere we can hide.
- No, no, no, no.
- Down there.
- We have to go. Now.
- James!
They have to die!
- Wait for me!
- I have no choice.
(dramatic music)
- [Pinocchio] Guys! Guys!
(thunder rumbling)
(mysterious music)
(lock clicking)
(ax thwacks)
(Mia screams)
(dramatic music)
(ax thwacking)
- Hide! Come on!
(dramatic music)
- You killed Dudley!
I fucking hate you!
- Shh, shh, shh, shh.
It's okay. I can bring
Dudley back, boy.
I can bring Dudley back and
I'll bring Mia back too.
James, James, this
was all for you, boy.
- No it wasn't. No it wasn't.
No it wasn't. No it wasn't.
- You disobeyed me, James.
Do you think those friends
wouldn't say anything?
They're children!
(ominous music)
(thunder rumbling)
- You're a monster!
(Geppetto breathing heavily)
- Let me in.
Let me in, James.
- No.
- Let me in.
- No! I fucking hate you!
- Let me in!
Open the fucking door!
(Geppetto shouting)
Now you're ruining everything!
Get out of the way, boy.
Get away from the
fucking door, kid!
(dramatic music)
(door banging)
(rain pattering)
(thunder rumbling)
Mia!
(water splashing)
(ax scraping)
Mia!
(puppet creaking)
Come out.
Come on, boys and girls.
(Pinocchio gasping)
(rain pattering)
I'm on the cusp of
something great.
Something bigger than you both.
(ax scraping)
You know I can't let you win.
No way.
Dr. Gammon showed me how
to bring you all back.
(ax scraping)
(Geppetto laughing)
(dramatic music)
(Mia shouting)
(ax thwacking)
(Geppetto spits)
(dramatic music)
(Mia yells)
You ruined everything.
(punches thudding)
It's time to die.
(ominous music)
(Geppetto grunts)
(Mia shouts)
(Mia screaming)
(ominous music)
You can all be my puppets!
(thunder rumbles)
(Mia screams)
(dramatic music)
(Geppetto shouts)
- Leave them alone.
- What the fuck?
- You forget yourself.
I made you.
- I'm not your puppet anymore.
- Yes you are.
Without me you're
just a piece of wood.
- No! I'm more than that.
- A puppet needs a master.
And I'm the only one
that can make you real.
Make you like James.
- I don't wanna be
like James anymore.
I just wanna be me.
- And you're always
gonna be hollow inside.
Incomplete, splintered,
and cracked.
- Pinocchio, don't listen.
- You, you can't
control me anymore.
- I gave you life!
I'm not only your
father, Pinocchio,
I'm your God!
And your God 'til I fucking die!
- Fuck you!
(dramatic music)
- Goodbye.
God.
(gunshot blasts)
(dramatic music)
(James gasping)
(cage door creaking)
(dramatic music)
(Geppetto screams)
- Holy fuck.
- Whoa!
- Ah!
(dramatic music)
(Geppetto's body thuds)
(ominous music)
(puppet growling)
(sparks hissing)
(dramatic music)
- James, we need to go.
- Come on!
(dramatic music)
(flames crackling)
(solemn music)
- James, are we still friends?
(gentle piano music)
Am I bad?
- You were just confused.
Just don't do it again, okay?
- I'm such a rascal, aren't I?
(Mia laughs)
- Yeah, besides, I mean they
were all assholes anyway.
Oh, except my dentist.
I'm gonna need a new dentist.
(Mia laughs)
- I'll get them too.
(James and Mia laughing)
You won't tell people
about me, will you?
- No lie.
- [Pinocchio] Good. Me too.
(distant siren wailing)
(Pinocchio giggles)
(mysterious music)
- Come on. Let's go.
- I'll catch up.
(sighs) Goodbye Father.
You made me. You can't
control me anymore.
James is mine.
(flames roaring)
(Wood Mother screaming)
- [Wood Mother] You Pinocchio!
(mysterious music)
- I didn't enjoy having to
kill them people, you know.
(mysterious music)
(Cricket coughing)
- That, that bloody kid.
I might be small, but I
have big plans for this one.
From roots come resurrection.
I'll bring you back, my master.
(dramatic music)
- This is behind the scenes.
And action.
Go on, go on, go on.
Oh!
(crew members chattering)
And roll camera.
- What's this?
(crew members laughing)
- High five?
- High five.
- Yeah.
- How's she doing?
- It's Kelly's stunt double.
(crew members laughing)
(bright music)
Yep.
And action on the coffin.
(Wood Mother coughing)
Action!
Roll sound.
- Open your mouth.
- Action.
Okay, camera set.
Here we go.
- It's taping too fast.
(crew members chattering)
In three, two, one, bang!
(playful music)
(crew members chattering)
And sparks.
What you doing today, Vince?
- Well, just a whole-
- Relax.
- Yeah, I think
that's great, guys.
Well done.
(cart rattling)
(light piano music)
- Yeah, as you go in,
you then bring the foot.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- [Crew Member] Maybe could
someone hold the head?
Would that help? I don't know.
- I think you see the head.
(crew members laughing)
- Hang on, wait a minute.
- Look at the arm.
- Chopped off.
- Oh fuck, my arm! Help!
(crew members chattering)
- Action.
Maybe he's like a spy.
He's looking around.
Like that, pointing it.
And three.
(crew members chattering)
- Good luck.
- I'm done.
(playful music)
- So you okay? Ready?
- Okay.
Okay, drop.
Professional film crew.
(puppeteer laughs)